{
    "id": "527e9a5a09fb41a1b191e5dbc43d24ef",
    "title": "Grammar exercise – is, am, are, was, were",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "04efba27f8c146b99613f7ef380ce10f",
            "title": "Is, Am, Are, Was, Were | Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What …………… you doing at 7’O clock in the morning?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "are",
                        "were",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………….. sleeping when the telephone rang.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "am",
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "When you phoned  I …………… working in the garden.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "am",
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "When I got up this morning the sun ………….. shining.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are",
                        "was"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘Have you finished that report?’ ‘I ………………. working on it.’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "am",
                        "was",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………….. painting all day yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "am",
                        "was",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The children ……………….. playing video games.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "are",
                        "is",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She …………………. working in the garden.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are",
                        "has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The teacher ……………. evaluating the answer sheets.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are",
                        "has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You can’t go out now. It …………….. raining cats and dogs.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "has",
                        "was"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}